A Guide to the Central Virginia Primetimers, Records,, 2002-2006
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
Special Collections and Archives, James Branch Cabell Library
Central Virginia Primetimers, Records, 2002-2006
Special Collections and Archives, James Branch Cabell Library
M353
0.32 linear feet.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the Central Virginia Primetimers in January 2006.
Historical Information
The Central Virginia Primetimers are the Richmond-area branch of the Primetimers World Wide, an organization formed to provide mature gay and bisexual men, and their admirers, with opportunities to come together in a supportive atmosphere to enjoy social, educational, and recreational activities. They were founded in December 2002.
Primetimers World Wide was founded in 1987 by a retired professor, Woody Baldwin. He felt a wide gap existed in today's society which caters almost exclusively to youth. Baldwin began the Boston Chapter first but the organization has grown to include over sixty chapters worldwide, located throughout North America, Europe and Australia.
Scope and Content
Records, 2002-2006, of the Central Virginia Primetimers principally consisting of board of directors minutes, newsletters, and officers' election ballots for the organization. Also magazine articles, funeral programs, and website printouts related to specific members.
Arrangement
Alphabetical.
Contents List
- Board of Directors minutes, December 2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Board of Directors minutes, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Board of Directors minutes, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Board of Directors minutes, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Brochures, ca. 2003 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Funeral program for Fain Miller, 8 January 2005 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Newsletters, February 2003-August 2005 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Officer election ballots (completed), 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Other Primetimers groups newsletters, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Richmond Magazine, article on Rick Smith and Gary Vaughan, October 2004 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Website printouts, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 11)